{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Land Clearing \u0026 Preparation Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40417/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40417,"taskName":"Building Site - Preparation and Clearing","taskDescription":"Clear Land and Prepare Building Site","xmTaskDescriptor":"Land Clearing \u0026 Preparation Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1403,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Building excavation excavate construction prepare","textMessagingName":"Site Prep","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically done before construction work begins.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes tree, brush removal \u0026 rough grading.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clear Land and Prepare Building Site.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Land Clearing \u0026 Site Preparation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":29,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Site Preparation","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Building Site - Preparation and Clearing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Site Preparation and Clearing Project","urlName":"Building-Site-Preparation-and-Clearing","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Land Clearing Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Site Preparation Costs | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Building,excavation,excavate,construction,prepare,Preparation,Clearing,clean,land,clear,Site","emcCategoryOid":-12028,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":709,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40417/":{"taskOID":40417,"originalTaskOID":40417,"setID":709,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4241,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Clearing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need to clear the site?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4892,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for building","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3462,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4891,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Prepare for appraisal or sale","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for appraisal or sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4242,"questionDisplayText":"Trees/Structures to Remove","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following currently exist on the site and will need to be removed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tree Stumps","answerDisplayText":"Tree Stumps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2411,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fences","answerDisplayText":"Fences","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1171,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Buildings","answerDisplayText":"Buildings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4243,"questionDisplayText":"Topography","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the topography that needs to be cleared. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Flat","answerDisplayText":"Flat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5802,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slightly sloped","answerDisplayText":"Slightly sloped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep Slope","answerDisplayText":"Steep Slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolling","answerDisplayText":"Rolling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4241,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Clearing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need to clear the site?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4892,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for building","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3462,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4891,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Prepare for appraisal or sale","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for appraisal or sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4892,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for building","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3462,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4891,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Prepare for appraisal or sale","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for appraisal or sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4242,"questionDisplayText":"Trees/Structures to Remove","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following currently exist on the site and will need to be removed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tree Stumps","answerDisplayText":"Tree Stumps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2411,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fences","answerDisplayText":"Fences","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1171,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Buildings","answerDisplayText":"Buildings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tree Stumps","answerDisplayText":"Tree Stumps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2411,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fences","answerDisplayText":"Fences","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1171,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Buildings","answerDisplayText":"Buildings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4243,"questionDisplayText":"Topography","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the topography that needs to be cleared. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Flat","answerDisplayText":"Flat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5802,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slightly sloped","answerDisplayText":"Slightly sloped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep Slope","answerDisplayText":"Steep Slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolling","answerDisplayText":"Rolling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Flat","answerDisplayText":"Flat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5802,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slightly sloped","answerDisplayText":"Slightly sloped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep Slope","answerDisplayText":"Steep Slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolling","answerDisplayText":"Rolling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}